fundera.com 2017-01-29

# Privacy Policy | Fundera

This Privacy Policy describes the information Fundera, Inc. (" ** _Fundera_** ," "we," "us" or "our") collects about you, how we use and share that information, and the privacy choices we offer.  This policy applies to information we collect when you register for Fundera's funding matching service, access or use our website, mobile applications, products, and services (collectively, the " ** _Services_** "), or when you otherwise interact with us.  As used in this Privacy Policy, the term " ** _Site_** " includes: all websites and all devices or applications operated by Fundera that collect personal information from you and that link to this Privacy Policy; pages within each such website, device, or application, any equivalent, mirror, replacement, substitute, or backup website, device, or application.  The use of the word "including" in this Agreement to refer to specific examples will be construed to mean "including, without limitation" or "including but not limited to" and will not be construed to mean that the examples given are an exclusive list of the topics covered.

|  | 

Our Privacy Policy helps you understand what information we collect, how we use or would potentially share that information, and the options we give you as a user. Unless otherwise noted, this covers all of your interactions with Fundera.  
  
---|---|---  
  
By accessing the Site and by using the Service, you agree to, and are bound by, this Privacy Policy.   **If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, you may not access or otherwise use this Site or Service**.

|  | 

We try our best to provide a clear, safe and fair privacy policy that respects the sensitivity of your data. If you review this document and find it unsatisfactory, please do send us your feedback at [**support@fundera.com**](mailto:support@fundera.com)!  
  
1.     Collection of Information

2.     Use of Your Information

3.     Sharing of Information

4.     Security

5.     Email Communications

6.     Short Message Service Communications

7.     Changes to Your Personal Information

8.     California Privacy Rights

9.     Business Transition

10.   Changes to Privacy Policy

11.   Contact Us

|  | 

Heres a handy table of contents.  
  
1.               _Collection of Information_.  Fundera may collect the following categories of personal information about you, including but not limited to the following:

|  |   
  
·         _Registration Information_ : When you register for the Service, you will be asked for basic registration information, such as a username and password.

·         _Identification Information_ : You may also be asked to provide identification information to confirm your identity, including your first and last name and certain financial information.

·         _Application Information_ : You may also be asked to provide additional information that will be provided to third-party sources of funding in connection with your applications for funding from those third-party sources, including certain financial information and other documents required by the third-party source of funding to complete an application.

·         _Third-Party Credentials_ : You may also enter in certain passwords, usernames, account numbers, and other account information for third-party sites and Internet services (" ** _Third-Party Sites_** ").

·         _Information from Third-Party Sites_ : In order to display information to you or to fulfill your requests for certain products and services through a Service, we may collect, on your behalf, your account and other personal information from Third-Party Sites that you register under your account via the Service.  We may also collect information about you from credit bureaus, mailing list providers, publicly available sources, and other third parties.

·         Additional Use of Third Parties: Fundera uses third parties to gather your data from financial institutions.  By using our Service, you grant our third-party provider the right, power, and authority to act on your behalf to access and transmit your personal and financial information from the relevant financial institution according to terms of our third-party providers privacy policy.

·         _Referral Partners_ : We may also collect application information, including personal information, about you from our third party referral partners.

**Other Information Collected** : Fundera may also collect the following: 

·         _Information Collected by Cookies and Web Beacons_ : We use various technologies to collect information, and this may include sending cookies to your computer or mobile device.  Cookies are small data files that are stored on your hard drive or in device memory by a website.  Among other things, cookies support the integrity of our registration process, retain your preferences and account settings, and help evaluate and compile aggregated statistics about user activity.  We may also collect information using web beacons.  Web beacons are electronic images that may be used in our Services or emails.  We may use web beacons to deliver cookies, count visits, understand usage, and determine whether an email has been opened and acted upon.

·         _Technical and Navigational Information_ : We may collect your computer browser type, Internet protocol address, pages visited, and average time spent on our Site.  This information may be used, for example, to alert you to software compatibility issues, or it may be analyzed to improve our web design and functionality.

|  | 

Here are some examples of information that you may share with us over the course of our time working together. We hope that a lot of this stuff is pretty obvioussuch as information related to your loan application that well need to assess your eligibility. Some are more technology-specific, such as cookies we use to help us customize your Fundera experience.  
  
2.               _Use of Your Information_.  We may use the information you provide about yourself and about your Third-Party Sites to fulfill your requests for our Services, to respond to your inquiries about our Services, and to offer you other products, programs, or services that we believe may be of interest to you.  We may use your information to complete transactions you request, to verify the existence and condition of your accounts, or to assist with a transaction.  For example, we may use the account information you provide or that we collect from Third-Party Sites to confirm your accounts are valid and, as applicable, to access funds from your accounts in connection with fulfillment of the Services.  We may also use your information to improve and personalize the Services and any related services, including future products and services.  For example, we may use your information to pre-fill form fields on the Sites for your convenience.

|  | 

So, here were just letting you know how well use your data to get you a loan that fits _your_ needs. A few examples:

1.      We may use your business information in order to secure loan eligibility feedback on your behalf.

2.      We may use login information that you provide for QuickBooks, in order to speed up your application process by pulling necessary data automatically.

3.      We might personalize our application based on what we know alreadyfor example, by pre-filling application fields if we know that information about you.  
  
3.               _Sharing of Information_.  We may share personal information about you as follows:

|  |   
  
·         With your consent, including to third-party credit reporting services when we request a credit report on your behalf or to any potential source of funding to whom you instruct us to identify you through the Services;

·         With third parties to provide, maintain, and improve our Services;

·         With any third party that referred you to the Services;

·         To respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal processes;

·         In order to investigate, prevent, defend against, or take other action regarding violations of our Terms of Service, illegal activities, suspected fraud, or situations involving potential threats to the legal rights or physical safety of any person or the security of our network, Sites or Services;

·         Non-personalized, anonymous data may be aggregated with data from other users and/or data sources and shared with partners or for marketing purposes;

·         To respond to claims that any posting or other content violates the rights of third parties;

·         In an emergency, to protect the health and safety of our Sites' users or the general public; or

·         As otherwise required by law.

|  |   
  
4.               _Security_.  We take reasonable measures, including firewall barriers, SSL encryption techniques, and authentication procedures, to help protect personal information from loss, theft, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.  You acknowledge, however, that no system is perfectly secure.  You use the Site and Services, and provide us with your personal information, at your own risk.

|  | 

The safety of your data is everything to us, and thats why we employ a number of bank-level security standards to protect your information.  
  
5.               _Email Communications_.  We may provide our registered customers with email alerts and summaries of their activity on the Service.  We may also allow users to subscribe to email newsletters and from time to time may transmit emails promoting Fundera or third-party goods or services.  Registered customers have the ability to opt out of receiving our promotional emails and to terminate their newsletter subscriptions by following the instructions in the emails.  Opting out in this manner will not end transmission of service-related emails, such as email alerts.

|  | 

In order to communicate reminders or other ongoing information about your account, well need to email you from time to time. That being said, our system emails will also include an option to unsubscribe.   
  
6.              _Short Message Service (SMS) Communications_. We may provide our registered customers with SMS alerts regarding their activity on the Service.  Registered customers have the ability to opt out of receiving these SMS alerts by texting the word STOP **to 1 (646) 760.3048. You may also reply STOP to any message you receive from us.**   Upon receipt of your STOP message, we will send you a SMS message to confirm that you have been unsubscribed.  At that point, you will no longer receive any further SMS messages from Fundera.  If you need any assistance, you can always text the word HELP to 1 (646) 760.3048 or reply "HELP" to any message you receive from us. Upon receipt of your "HELP" message, we will respond with "STOP" instructions and a link to relevant Terms of Service and Privacy Policy. 

|  |   
  
7.               _Changes to Your Personal Information_.  If you wish to access personal information that you have submitted to us or to request the correction of any inaccurate information you have submitted to us, you may correct certain information via your user account.  Alternatively, you can contact us at support@fundera.com to request any corrections to your personal information.  You may also email us if you wish to deregister, but even after you deregister, we may retain archived copies of information about you for a period of time that is consistent with applicable law.

|  | 

If you would like us to modify or delete any information youve submitted, you can use your account dashboard. But, if thats too much of a hassle, dont worry. You can just email [**support@fundera.com**](mailto:support@fundera.com) **** at any time. In some cases, we may need to retain records of your account consistent with the laws under which we operate, but generally you should feel confident that you have control over the data you submit to us.  
  
8.               _California Privacy Rights_.  California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the "Shine The Light" law, permits our customers who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year.  If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request to policy@fundera.com. In your request, please attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for our response. Please be aware that not all information sharing is covered by the California Privacy Rights requirements and only information on covered sharing will be included in our response.

|  |   
  
9\.                   _Business Transition_.  In the event another entity merges with or acquires Fundera or substantially all of its assets, your personal information may be transferred to that successor or acquiring entity.  A court may also order the sale of personal information as an asset in a bankruptcy or similar insolvency proceeding. 

10.               _Changes to Privacy Policy_.  We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time, so please review it frequently. You may review updates to our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy at any time via links on http://fundera.com.  Consistent with our Terms of Service, you agree to accept electronic communications and/or postings of revised versions of this Privacy Policy on http://fundera.com and agree that such electronic communications or postings constitute notice to you of the revised version of this Privacy Policy.  Changes take effect immediately upon posting.

11.               Contact Us.  If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at [**support@fundera.com**](mailto:support@fundera.com).

|  | 

We rarely make changes to our Privacy Policy, but were always striving to make it better, so we may revise it from time to time as our business evolves.
